NO BOY NO CRY ore zenshin GO
no boy, no cry, I advance go!
shounen yo kiite kure
hey boys, listen up
ningen nante taishita mon ja nai sa
humans aren't such a big deal
ashita nante moui ranai kara
who needs tomorrow anyway
nigitta kobushi wo kakusu na yo
so don't hide your fists
fuan ni yume wo
you're not old enough
uri tobasu hodo mada oiborechainai daro
to sell your dreams away to uncertainty
shounen yo kokoro no jyuu no
hey boys, you're the only ones
hikigane wo hikeru no wa kimi dake sa
who can pull the trigger in your heart
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
doushi yo mo naku kudaranai
we're living in this senseless, ridiculous,
kono subarashii sekai ni tattaima ikiteiru kara
awesome world right at this moment,
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
subete no hontou to uso wo
don't forget every truth or lie
kesshite wasurete shima wa nai you ni
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
shinu ni wa mosugiru darou
we're way too young to die
shiraketa tsura ga naranderu karappo no kono machi de
in this empty town lined with empty faces
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids took off
kaze no nai kono yoru ni
into this windless night
nanika wo kaeyou to shiteru kara
because they want to change something
{The Two Heartbeats:
{Kabuto's Trap
Huh?!
It can't be!
Even if you put up a bluff
I can foresee...
that you are already... finished.
Poor thing.
This child is trembling
like a puppy.
Now Kabuto...
Get rid of her
but don't make her suffer.
I understand.
Sasuke...
I-I'll do anything for you!
So I'm begging you...
Please stay here!
You are really annoying.
Please don't go!
Sakura...
Thank you...
Sasuke...
Wait!
Hmm?
Did you... say something?
Wait!
Where's Sasuke!
Where is Sasuke?
It couldn't be that...
your body is already Sasuke's...?
There's no need to keep it
a secret any longer.
It's all right Kabuto
go on and tell her.
He was a little late
in getting here.
Orochimaru-sama wasn't able to
wait for Sasuke
and already had been reincarnated
into another vessel.
So Sasuke is all right?!
Somewhere in this building...
Orochimaru-sama gave Sasuke
the Curse Mark
so he could wait for
the next opportunity to reincarnate.
But...
Not all humans can
tolerate Curse Marks.
No way, there's no way
that Sasuke could be...
That's right, Sasuke wasn't able
to tolerate the Curse Mark
and so he died.
That's a lie.
It has to be a lie!
What would telling a lie
like that accomplish?
To someone that's going to die...
As you are?
If you want to see him that badly
I'll let you see him.
When you die you can see him
in the other world.
Sasuke...
Sakura!
Sakura, don't you believe...
what a guy like him says!
Naruto!
So it's Naruto, I thought you'd drowned
and died a long time ago but...
When I make a promise
I don't give up.
That's my Way of Ninja!
I ain't gonna die
until I get Sasuke back!
This is interesting!
Sakura go hide!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
I'm over here!
Hey stupid, over here!
Over here, over here!
Where're you looking?
I'm over here! Over here!
What're you doing? Hey!
So you've used up all
your Kunai Knives...
I'm gonna... completely blow you away!
How annoying!
Fire Style:
Misty Flames Dance Jutsu!
— Ouch!
— That's hot!
— Yikes!
— Oww!
You're too slow!
Rasengan!
Naruto!
Since you and Orochimaru are here
it means Sasuke is probably here too!
Tell us the truth right now!
Wh-What the heck?
My body won't move...
Have a good look at yourself.
Wh-What's this?
Those are Chakra Threads.
Chakra Threads?
While you were attacking earlier
I wrapped the thread around you.
Take a good look at where
that thread is connected.
That's right.
Those Chakra Threads are...
connected to my heart's
Chakra Network.
And Naruto the thread that's
wrapped around you
is connected through my Chakra Network
to your organs and to your heart.
See can you hear that?
My heart and your heart will
eventually become connected as one!
— Damn!
— Naruto!
It's no use. That thread is formulated
and spun with Chakra
and it will absolutely not break.
Now our hearts are
completely synchronized...
The Chakra which passes
through this thread
via the Chakra Network from my heart
is controlling your heart you see.
It's no use even though
it's my heart...
If my heart beat gets faster
your heart will get faster too...
And when my heart stops beating...
you will die too!
Don't! If you stop your heart
you'll die too!
That's right.
But that doesn't mean much.
Since I've already promised
my body to Orochimaru-sama...
Wh-What the heck are
you gonna do?!
If I crush this heart...
you will die too!
Now together we will...
Naruto!
How's it feel to have
your heart seized?
It'll be all right...
You'll be out of your misery
right away!
Stop it!
How foolish, if you kill me
Naruto will die too.
What I'm gonna cut...
is this!
There's no use you know
It's impossible to cut thread formulated
and made from Chakra.
Even Tsunade-sama's great strength
wouldn't be able to break it.
What should I...
What should I do?!
Naruto is suffering right
in front of my eyes and yet...
I can't do anything!
Sakura...!
I... absolutely will not lose!
Until I've fulfilled my promise!
You bravado ends there.
Now shall we die together?
And go to the place where
Sasuke is waiting?
Naruto!
Sakura!
— Sasame?!
— Sakura...
Stick this tag on a Kunai Knife!
Naruto!
Naruto?!
Hey, are you okay? Naruto!
No way...
It can't be...
No way!
Naruto!
Ahh... My chest right now
is beating with joy.
Idiot! It was a waste for me
to have worried!
Sorry Sakura...
You're so worthless!
That's right, Sasame!
Why are you here?
Well it's...
I was saved by Sasame
you know.
Me too.
What do you mean?
Water came rushing into that
trap pit we were in earlier...
That's it! The lid to the pit!
Damn!
When the water reached
the ceiling
I desperately tried to open the lid
but wasn't able to escape...
I was told by Master Jiraiya
to go to where Hanzaki is.
But I got concerned about Arashi
so I came...
Naruto!
Hey! Thanks!
Th-The frog spoke...!
Well come to think of it,
there's no way you could open the lid
of the trap by pushing on it.
Geez!
But how come the thread that
I couldn't cut with the Kunai Knife
be cut when I wrapped it
with Sasame's tag?
Because the Chakra Thread
is a Secret Technique
within the secrets of
our Fuuma Ninja Technique...
Of the Fuuma?!
Oh, I see...
So who the hell is this?!
Oh!
She is... from earlier!
Mistress Kagero...
She's a Fuuma Jonin.
Sasame!
Sasame...
I was resurrected
by Orochimaru-sama...
You! You're being tricked
by Orochimaru!
Where is Sasuke?
And Arashi?
Where's Sasame's cousin!
Orochimaru-sama is...
going to raise our Fuuma clan...
to the center stage
of Shinobi again.
You're still talking about
that stuff?!
At least tell Sasame the truth!
So it's there! He's in there!
Sasame and Arashi...
You two were so close...
Then it'd be better
if you didn't see him.
Mistress Kagero...
What do you want to do, Sasame?
Do you want to wait here?
I will see him!
No matter what's in store for me!
I came all the way here
to see Arashi!
Yeah! You've got guts!
All right! Let's go together!
Yeah! Let's go!
Sasame...
There might be some sort of trap...
Leave it to me!
Orochimaru?!
Good of you to come, Sasame...
Why...?
Arashi...!
Arashi!
Arashi?
I'm no longer...
Arashi...
Wh-What the heck is going on?!
The skills and bodies of the Fuuma Jonin
were combined into one...
and I've been reborn as
the ultimate Ninja you see...
Now I'll show you
my ultimate Ninjutsu... Sasame!
No... Arashi...
Damn Orochimaru!
I will not forgive him
no matter what!
hitotsu hitotsu omoidaseba
when I recalled the parts one by one,
subete wakatteita kigashite ita no ni
I felt as though I had understood everything
iroaseta kotoba wa
faded words
boku no sugu soba ni oite atta
which I kept so close to me
kotae no denai yoru to
speechless nights,
a hint of warmth,
hitokira no nukumori to
and this distant yearning for you
haruka kanata no akogare to
I live,
tada sore dake wo
simply repeating this cycle
kurikaeshi boku wa ikite iru
held in my two hands
kono ryoute ni kakaete iru mono
a droplet of time
toki no shizuku
softly clutching forgotten memories
sotto nigirishimete wasureta kioku
lost words
nakushita kotoba
I'll keep these thoughts...
kono omoi wa
Sorry... I'm sorry Naruto.
I haven't been able to do anything
after all.
I'm always dragging you down.
I hadn't changed at all.
But Naruto Sasame
you two taught me.
That's why I want to change
the kind of person I am!
This time this time
it's my turn to give it my all!
Next time:
"Sakura's Decision."